They will hunt you.
Werewolves is a action, horror, thriller film directed by Steven C. Miller.
A year after a supermoon’s light activated a dormant gene, transforming humans into bloodthirsty werewolves
and causing nearly a billion deaths, the nightmare resurfaces as the supermoon rises again.
Two scientists attempt to stop the mutation but fail and must
now struggle to reach one of their family homes.
Dr. Wesley Marshall, played by Frank Grillo.
Dr. Amy Chen, played by Katrina Law.
Lucy Marshall, played by Ilfenesh Hadera.
Cody, played by Jimmy Cummings.
Dr. Aranda, played by Lou Diamond Phillips.
Emma Marshall, played by Kamdynn Gary.
Werewolves is a 2024 American action horror film
directed and produced by Steven C.
It stars Frank Grillo, Katrina Law, Ilfenesh Hadera, James
Michael Cummings, and Lou Diamond Phillips.
The story takes place on the night of a supermoon event that causes humans to turn into werewolves,
which first occurred the preceding year, and follows the attempts to control the situation.
The film was released theatrically in the United States
on December 6, 2024, to mixed reviews.
The film explores themes of moonlight, werewolf, mysterious, intense.
The tone is dark and intense.